Simon Fraser University Library fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Loans Division records, 1964 - 1998; F-50-7; 1.74 m of textual records
  - Reports and statistics, 1965 - 1998; F-50-7-2; 31 cm of textual records
    - Monthly Reports, 1975; F-50-7-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-46)
    - Monthly Reports, 1976; F-50-7-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-46)
    - Monthly Reports, 1977; F-50-7-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-46)
    - Monthly Reports, 1978; F-50-7-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 50-46)
    - Statistics (daily), 1965 - 1969; F-50-7-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 50-46)
    - Statistics (daily), 1970 - 1974; F-50-7-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 50-46)
    - Statistics (daily), 1975 - 1979; F-50-7-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 50-46)
    - Statistics (daily), 1980; F-50-7-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 50-46)
    - Statistics (monthly), 1967 - 1970; F-50-7-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 50-46)
    - Statistics (monthly), 1971 - 1975; F-50-7-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 50-46)
    - Statistics (monthly), 1976 - 1979; F-50-7-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 50-46)
    - Turnstile Count (Monthly), 1981; F-50-7-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 50-46)
    - Turnstile Count (Monthly), 1982; F-50-7-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 50-46)
    - Turnstile Count (Monthly), 1983; F-50-7-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 50-46)
    - Loans policy revisions, vol. 1, 1992 - 1998; F-50-7-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 50-85)
    - Loans policy revisions, vol. 2, 1992 - 1998; F-50-7-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 50-85)
    - SHARE project - agreement with Okanagan College, Kelowna, 1977 - 1982; F-50-7-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 50-85)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/53.
  - Interlibrary loans, 1964 - 1997; F-50-7-3; 34 cm of textual records
    - Interlibrary (Daily), 1973 - 1974; F-50-7-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - Interlibrary (Daily), 1974 - 1975; F-50-7-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - ILL/UBC Statistics, 1973 - 1974; F-50-7-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - ILL/UBC Statistics, 1974 - 1975; F-50-7-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - ILL/UBC Statistics, 1975 - 1977; F-50-7-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - Interlibrary loans general statistics, 1970; F-50-7-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - Interlibrary loans general statistics, 1971; F-50-7-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - Interlibrary loans general statistics, 1972; F-50-7-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - Interlibrary loans general statistics, 1973; F-50-7-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - Interlibrary loans general statistics, 1974; F-50-7-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - Interlibrary loans general statistics, 1975; F-50-7-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - Interlibrary loans general statistics, 1976; F-50-7-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - Interlibrary loans general statistics, 1977; F-50-7-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - Interlibrary loans general statistics, 1978; F-50-7-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - Interlibrary loans general statistics, 1979; F-50-7-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - Interlibrary loans general statistics, 1980; F-50-7-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - Interlibrary loans general statistics, 1981; F-50-7-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - Interlibrary loans general statistics, 1982; F-50-7-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 50-47)
    - BC Post Secondary Interlibrary loan network statistics, 1980; F-50-7-3-0-19 (Archival box - small 50-48)
    - BC Post Secondary Interlibrary loan Network statistics, 1981; F-50-7-3-0-20 (Archival box - small 50-48)
    - BC Post Secondary Interlibrary loan Network statistics, 1982; F-50-7-3-0-21 (Archival box - small 50-48)
    - BC Post Secondary Interlibrary loan Network statistics, 1983; F-50-7-3-0-22 (Archival box - small 50-48)
    - BC Post Secondary Interlibrary loan Network statistics, 1984; F-50-7-3-0-23 (Archival box - small 50-48)
    - BC Post Secondary Interlibrary loan Network statistics, 1985; F-50-7-3-0-24 (Archival box - small 50-48)
    - BC Post Secondary Interlibrary loan Network statistics, 1986; F-50-7-3-0-25 (Archival box - small 50-48)
    - BC Post Secondary Interlibrary loan Network statistics, 1987; F-50-7-3-0-26 (Archival box - small 50-48)
    - Policy, procedures and assessments, 1977 - 1984; F-50-7-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 50-86)
      Creator's original file classification code: 400/12/3.
    - Interlibrary loan charges, 1993 - 1996; F-50-7-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 50-86)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/33.
    - Correspondence, vol. 1, 1964 - 1986; F-50-7-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 50-86)
    - Correspondence, vol. 2, 1964 - 1986; F-50-7-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 50-86)
    - Correspondence, vol. 3, 1964 - 1986; F-50-7-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 50-86)
    - Correspondence, vol. 4, 1964 - 1986; F-50-7-3-0-32 (Archival box - standard 50-86)
    - Correspondence, vol. 5, 1964 - 1986; F-50-7-3-0-33 (Archival box - standard 50-86)
    - Correspondence, 1993 - 1997; F-50-7-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 50-87)
  - Reserve loans, 1967 - 1982; F-50-7-4; 13 cm of textual records
    - Reserve loans statistics, 1972 - 1981; F-50-7-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-49)
    - Reserve loans statistics, 1967 - 1969; F-50-7-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-49)
    - Reserve loans statistics, 1970 - 1971; F-50-7-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-49)
    - Reserve loans statistics, 1972 - 1973; F-50-7-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-49)
    - Reserve loans statistics, 1974 - 1975; F-50-7-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-49)
    - Reserve loans statistics, 1976 - 1977; F-50-7-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-49)
    - Reserve loans statistics, 1978 - 1980; F-50-7-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-49)
    - Reserve loans statistics, 1981; F-50-7-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-49)
    - Reserve loans statistics, 1982; F-50-7-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-49)
  - Budget, 1975 - 1986; F-50-7-5; 13 cm of textual records
    - Budget, 1975 - 1976; F-50-7-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-50)
    - Budget, 1976 - 1977; F-50-7-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-50)
    - Budget, 1977 - 1978; F-50-7-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-50)
    - Budget, 1978 - 1979; F-50-7-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-50)
    - Budget, 1979 - 1980; F-50-7-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-50)
    - Budget, 1980 - 1981; F-50-7-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-50)
    - Budget, 1981 - 1982; F-50-7-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-50)
    - Budget, 1982 - 1983; F-50-7-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-50)
    - Budget, 1983 - 1984; F-50-7-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-50)
    - Budget, 1984 - 1986; F-50-7-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-50)
- Information Systems Division records, 1964 - 1999; F-50-8; 1.36 m of textual records
  Series consists of records related to the Information Systems Division of the University Library and includes correspondence between Library staff and EPIC, GEAC, and BRS System database vendors; vendor proposals and purchase agreements; automation reports and database planning records; monthly division activity reports; GEAC project planning, training, and implementation; and minutes of the GEAC Acquisition Planning Committee, RFP Steering Committee, Name and Address System Steering Committee, and the British Columbia Library Network.
  Records include correspondence and working papers, minutes, reports and statistics, project proposals and updates, and contracts, agreements, and invoices.
  British Columbia Library Network; National Library of Canada
  For further records relating to the British Columbia Union Catalogue (BCUC), please see series F-50-12, for the records of Tri University Libraries consortium.
  - Correspondence and memoranda, 1964 - 1999; F-50-8-1; 83 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1964 - 1968; F-50-8-1-0-1 (Archival box - small 50-51)
    - Correspondence, 1969 - 1973; F-50-8-1-0-2 (Archival box - small 50-51)
    - Correspondence, 1974 - 1980; F-50-8-1-0-3 (Archival box - small 50-51)
    - Memoranda, 1967 - 1970; F-50-8-1-0-4 (Archival box - small 50-52)
    - Memoranda, 1971 - 1972; F-50-8-1-0-5 (Archival box - small 50-52)
    - Memoranda, 1973 - 1975; F-50-8-1-0-6 (Archival box - small 50-52)
    - Memoranda, 1976 - 1977; F-50-8-1-0-7 (Archival box - small 50-52)
    - Memoranda, 1978 - 1980; F-50-8-1-0-8 (Archival box - small 50-52)
    - Systems correspondence, vol. 1, 1971 - 1983; F-50-8-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-87)
    - Systems correspondence, vol. 2, 1971 - 1983; F-50-8-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-87)
    - GEAC project planning, vol. 1, 1984; F-50-8-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-87)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/54f.
    - GEAC project planning, vol. 2, 1984; F-50-8-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-88)
    - GEAC proposal to SFU, 1984; F-50-8-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-88)
    - Library system planning documents, 1984 - 1985; F-50-8-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-88)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/54a.
    - GEAC Acquisition Planning Committee, 1985; F-50-8-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-88)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/54b.
    - GEAC/SFU purchase agreement, 1985; F-50-8-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-88)
    - GEAC agreements, 1987 - 1994; F-50-8-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 50-88)
    - GEAC library correspondence, vol. 1, 1984 - 1986; F-50-8-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 50-89)
    - GEAC library correspondence, vol. 2, 1984 - 1986; F-50-8-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 50-89)
    - GEAC library correspondence, vol. 3, 1984 - 1986; F-50-8-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 50-89)
    - GEAC library correspondence, vol. 1, 1987 - 1988; F-50-8-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 50-89)
    - GEAC library correspondence, vol. 2, 1987 - 1988; F-50-8-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 50-89)
    - GEAC library correspondence, vol. 1, 1989 - 1994; F-50-8-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 50-89)
    - GEAC library correspondence, vol. 2, 1989 - 1994; F-50-8-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 50-90)
    - GEAC barcoding project, vol. 1, 1986 - 1987; F-50-8-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 50-90)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/54c.
    - GEAC barcoding project, vol. 2, 1986 - 1987; F-50-8-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 50-90)
    - GEAC 9000 upgrade, 1989 - 1991; F-50-8-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 50-90)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/54e.
    - GEAC conversion to 9000, vol. 1, 1989 - 1994; F-50-8-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 50-90)
    - GEAC conversion to 9000, vol. 2, 1989 - 1994; F-50-8-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 50-90)
    - GEAC conversion to 9000, vol. 3, 1989 - 1994; F-50-8-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 50-90)
    - BRS System purchase, 1991 - 1994; F-50-8-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 50-91)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/54g.
    - GEAC replacement system, vol. 1, 1992 - 1994; F-50-8-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 50-91)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/54h.
    - GEAC replacement system, vol. 2, 1992 - 1994; F-50-8-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 50-91)
    - GEAC replacement system, vol. 3, 1992 - 1994; F-50-8-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 50-91)
    - System optimization report, 1992; F-50-8-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 50-91)
    - GLIS migration to Advance (GMA), 1993; F-50-8-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 50-91)
    - Working RFP, 1993; F-50-8-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 50-91)
    - New system reports, 1993 - 1994; F-50-8-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 50-91)
    - ELN agreements, 1993; F-50-8-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 50-92)
    - RFP Steering Committee, 1994; F-50-8-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 50-92)
    - Innovative Interfaces (III) agreement, 1994; F-50-8-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 50-92)
    - Systems agreements, 1994 - 1999; F-50-8-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 50-92)
    - National Library of Canada (NLC) Digital Libraries, 1997 - 1998; F-50-8-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 50-92)
    - Systems planning, 1997 - 1999; F-50-8-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 50-92)
    - Systems ACS review, 1998; F-50-8-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 50-92)
  - Division reports, 1969 - 1978; F-50-8-2; 13 cm of textual records
    Records are numbered arranged chronologically.
    - Reports L/ISD/1-6, 1969 - 1970; F-50-8-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-53)
    - Reports L/ISD/7-14, 1970; F-50-8-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-53)
    - Reports L/ISD/15-17, 1970; F-50-8-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-53)
    - Reports L/ISD/18-20, 1970; F-50-8-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-53)
    - Reports L/ISD/21-2, 1971; F-50-8-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-53)
    - Reports L/ISD/23-27, 1971 - 1972; F-50-8-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-53)
    - Monthly Reports, 1975 - 1978; F-50-8-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-53)
    - Annual Reports, 1969 - 1976; F-50-8-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-53)
  - General reports and papers, 1967 - 1979; F-50-8-3; 13 cm of textual records
    - Papers and Reports, 1967 - 1968; F-50-8-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-54)
    - Papers and Reports, 1969; F-50-8-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-54)
    - Papers and Reports, 1970; F-50-8-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-54)
    - Papers and Reports, 1970 - 1971; F-50-8-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-54)
    - Papers and Reports, 1971; F-50-8-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-54)
    - Papers and Reports, 1972; F-50-8-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-54)
    - Papers and Reports, 1973 - 1974; F-50-8-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-54)
    - Papers and Reports, 1975 - 1979; F-50-8-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-54)
  - Project proposals, 1971 - 1975; F-50-8-4; 7 cm of textual records
    Proposals are numbered and arranged chronologically.
    - ISC Project Proposals, No 1-26, 1971 - 1975; F-50-8-4-0-1 (Archival box - small 50-55)
    - ISC Project Reports, No 1-5, 1971 - 1972; F-50-8-4-0-2 (Archival box - small 50-55)
    - ISC Project Reports, No 6-22, 1972; F-50-8-4-0-3 (Archival box - small 50-55)
    - ISC Project Reports, No 23-31, 1973; F-50-8-4-0-4 (Archival box - small 50-55)
    - Systems Tasks, No 1-13, 1973 - 1974; F-50-8-4-0-5 (Archival box - small 50-55)
    - Simulation Project, 1972 - 1973; F-50-8-4-0-6 (Archival box - small 50-55)
  - Name and address system, 1976 - 1978; F-50-8-5; 7 cm of textual records
    - Name and Address System - Steering Committee Minutes, 1976 - 1977; F-50-8-5-0-1 (Archival box - small 50-56)
    - Name and Address System - Steering Committee Minutes, 1977 - 1978; F-50-8-5-0-2 (Archival box - small 50-56)
    - Epic Data System Meetings - Minutes, 1978; F-50-8-5-0-3 (Archival box - small 50-56)
  - British Columbia Union Catalogue, 1977 - 1985; F-50-8-6; 15 cm of textual records
    - Minutes of Committees, 1982; F-50-8-6-0-1 (Archival box - small 50-57)
    - British Columbia Library Network, 1980; F-50-8-6-0-2 (Archival box - small 50-57)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1977 - 1985; F-50-8-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-93)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/17.
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1977 - 1985; F-50-8-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-93)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 3, 1977 - 1985; F-50-8-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-93)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 4, 1977 - 1985; F-50-8-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-93)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 5, 1977 - 1985; F-50-8-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-93)
- Committee records, 1966 - 1997; F-50-9; 1.98 m of textual records 173 photographs: prints; black and white; Physical description: 173 photographs located in F-50-9-8-0-9
  Series consists of records relating to the University Librarian's correspondence with, and participation on, various university and non-university committees.
  For the complete list of committees, see the sub-series list below.
  Records include correspondence and working papers, agendas and minutes, reports, financial papers and staff photographs.
  - Collection Committees, 1968 - 1989; F-50-9-1; 23 cm of textual records
    - Terms of Reference, 1968; F-50-9-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Collection Divisions Committee, 1968; F-50-9-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Collection Divisions Committee, 1969; F-50-9-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Collection Divisions Committee, 1970; F-50-9-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Collection Divisions Committee, 1971; F-50-9-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Collection Divisions Committee, 1972; F-50-9-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Collection Divisions Committee, 1973; F-50-9-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Collection Divisions Committee, 1974; F-50-9-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Collection Divisions Committee, 1975; F-50-9-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Collection Development Committee, 1977 - 1978; F-50-9-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Collection Development Committee, 1979 - 1980; F-50-9-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982 - 1984; F-50-9-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Collection Divisions Committee Papers, C84-C99, 1968; F-50-9-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Collection Divisions Committee Papers, C100-C124, 1968 - 1969; F-50-9-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Collection Divisions Committee Papers, C125-C138, 1969 - 1970; F-50-9-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Collection Divisions Committee Memoranda, 1968 - 1973; F-50-9-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Processing Divisions Committee - Terms of Reference, 1969; F-50-9-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Processing Divisions Committee, 1969 - 1974; F-50-9-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 50-58)
    - Collections Development Committee minutes and correspondence, vol. 1, 1969 - 1989; F-50-9-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 50-93)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/42.
    - Collections Development Committee minutes and correspondence, vol. 2, 1969 - 1989; F-50-9-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 50-94)
    - Collections Development Committee minutes and correspondence, vol. 3, 1969 - 1989; F-50-9-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 50-94)
    - Collections Development Committee minutes and correspondence, vol. 4, 1969 - 1989; F-50-9-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 50-94)
    - Collections Management Committee minutes and correspondence, 1984 - 1985; F-50-9-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 50-94)
  - Division Heads Committee, 1967 - 1976; F-50-9-2; 6 cm of textual records
    - Division Heads Committee, 1967 - 1968; F-50-9-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
    - Division Heads Committee, 1969; F-50-9-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
    - Division Heads Committee, 1970; F-50-9-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
    - Division Heads Committee, 1971 - 1972; F-50-9-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
    - Division Heads Committee Papers, D159-D185, 1967 - 1968; F-50-9-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
    - Division Heads Committee Papers, D186-D210, 1968 - 1969; F-50-9-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
    - Division Heads Committee Papers, D211-D229, 1969 - 1970; F-50-9-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
    - Division Heads Committee Meetings/Minutes, 1974 - 1976; F-50-9-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
  - Information Systems Committee, 1966 - 1977; F-50-9-3; 11 cm of textual records
    - Information Systems Committee - Terms of Reference, 1968 - 1971; F-50-9-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
    - Information Systems Committee, 1967 - 1969; F-50-9-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
    - Information Systems Committee, 1971 - 1972; F-50-9-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
    - Information Systems Committee - Papers A1-A21, 1966 - 1971; F-50-9-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
    - Information Systems Committee Memoranda, 1968 - 1972; F-50-9-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
    - Information Systems Committee minutes and correspondence, vol. 1, 1971 - 1977; F-50-9-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-94)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/9.
    - Information Systems Committee minutes and correspondence, vol. 1, 1971 - 1977; F-50-9-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-94)
    - Information Systems Committee projects and reports, 1969 - 1971; F-50-9-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-95)
    - Information Systems Committee project binder, 1969 - 1971; F-50-9-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-95)
  - Administration committee, 1969 - 1975; F-50-9-4; 6 cm of textual records
    - Administration Committee, 1969 - 1970; F-50-9-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
    - Administration Committee Papers EC1-EC20 (index), 1970; F-50-9-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
    - Administration Committee, 1971; F-50-9-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
    - Administration Committee Papers EC21-EC42 (index), 1971; F-50-9-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
    - Administration Committee, 1972; F-50-9-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
    - Administration Committee, 1973; F-50-9-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
    - Administration Committee, 1974 - 1975; F-50-9-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
    - Administration Committee Related Meetings, 1973 - 1975; F-50-9-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
  - Educational Services Committee, 1971 - 1972; F-50-9-5; 1 cm of textual records
    - Educational Services Committee - Terms of Reference, 1971 - 1972; F-50-9-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
    - Educational Services Committee, 1971 - 1972; F-50-9-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
  - Staff Appointment Committee, 1968; F-50-9-6; 1 cm of textual records
    - Staff Appointment Committee, 1968; F-50-9-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
    - Personnel Selection Procedure Committee, 1968; F-50-9-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
  - Personnel Committee, 1968 - 1972; F-50-9-7; 8 cm of textual records
    - Personnel Committee - Terms of Reference, 1969; F-50-9-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
    - Personnel Committee, 1969 - 1972; F-50-9-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
    - Policy and procedures, 1968 - 1970; F-50-9-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-95)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/7.
    - Correspondence, 1968 - 1971; F-50-9-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-95)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/8.
    - Minutes and reports, 1969 - 1970; F-50-9-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-95)
    - Minutes and reports, 1971 - 1972; F-50-9-7-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-95)
  - Staff Committee, 1968 - 1975; F-50-9-8; 15 cm of textual records 173 photographs: prints; black and white
    - Staff Committee - Terms of Reference, 1970; F-50-9-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
    - Staff Committee, 1970; F-50-9-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
    - Staff Committee, 1971; F-50-9-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
    - Staff Committee, 1972; F-50-9-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
    - Staff Committee, 1973; F-50-9-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
    - Staff Committee, 1974; F-50-9-8-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
    - Staff Committee, 1975; F-50-9-8-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
    - Staff Committee - Memoranda, 1971 - 1975; F-50-9-8-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-60)
    - Staff Photographs, 1970; F-50-9-8-0-9 (Archival box - small 50-113)
      Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Correspondence and minutes, vol. 1, 1968 - 1972; F-50-9-8-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-95)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/1.